const preIntermediateQuestionSetOne = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "apple",
        status: 0,
        question: "With A, which fruit is small and usually red or green?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "ball",
        status: 0,
        question: "With B, what is round and used in many sports?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "cat",
        status: 0,
        question: "With C, what animal is small and makes a meow sound?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "dice",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what do people throw when they play a board game?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "eggs",
        status: 0,
        question: "With E, what food do we get from Chickens? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "fish",
        status: 0,
        question: "With F, what animal swims in water?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "go",
        status: 0,
        question: 'With G, what word is the opposite of "stop"?',
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "hello",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With H, what five letter word do people say when they meet someone?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "ice cream",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With I, what do people like to eat on a hot day? (two words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jelly",
        status: 0,
        question: "With J, what dessert wobbles? Children like to eat it.",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "king",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, the female is a queen. What is the male?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "love",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, what does a heart shape often mean?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "monkey",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, which animal swings in trees?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "nine",
        status: 0,
        question: "With N, what is four plus five?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "octopus",
        status: 0,
        question: "With O, which animal has eight tentacles?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "piano",
        status: 0,
        question: "With P, what has black and white keys and plays music?",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quiet",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Q, what word means no talking?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "raining",
        status: 0,
        question: "With R, you should take an umbrella because it's ...",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "saturday",
        status: 0,
        question: "With S, what day comes after Friday?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "trees",
        status: 0,
        question: "With T, what has leaves and grows outside? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "ufos",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With U, what do people sometimes see in the sky? Maybe there are aliens inside. (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "violin",
        status: 0,
        question: "With V, what looks like a small guitar and plays music?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "watermelon",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With W, which fruit is green on the outside, red on the inside and often very big?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "xray",
        status: 0,
        question: "With X, what do doctors take to look at bones?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yellow",
        status: 0,
        question:
            'With Y, "We all live in a ... submarine, ... submarine, ... submarine."',
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zoo",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, where do people sometimes go to see animals?",
    },
];

const preIntermediateQuestionSetTwo = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "aeroplane",
        status: 0,
        question: "With A, what helps people fly in the sky?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "breakfast",
        status: 0,
        question: "With B, what do people eat in the morning?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "chair",
        status: 0,
        question: "With C, what do children sit on at school?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "die",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what do all people do at the end of their life?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "english",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With E, the French are from France and the ... are from England.",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "fourteen",
        status: 0,
        question: "With F, what is seven plus seven?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "giraffe",
        status: 0,
        question: "With G, which animal has a long neck?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "happy",
        status: 0,
        question: "With H, if someone is smiling, how are they feeling?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "ice skating",
        status: 0,
        question: "With I, what do you do at an ice rink? (two words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jam",
        status: 0,
        question: "With J, what do people sometimes put on bread or toast?",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kangaroo",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, which animal hops and lives in Australia?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "leg",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, which body parts do you put in your jeans? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "menu",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, what shows the food and drinks in a restaurant?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "no",
        status: 0,
        question: "With N, what do you say when you disagree?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "orange",
        status: 0,
        question: "With O, which colour can people eat?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "ping pong",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With P, which has a small white ball and is played on a table? (2 words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "queen",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Q, the male is a king. What is the female?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "rainbow",
        status: 0,
        question: "With R, what has seven colours and is sometimes in the sky?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "school",
        status: 0,
        question: "With S, where do children go every morning?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "television",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With T, what do people watch in the living room? (use the full word)",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "umbrella",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, what do people use when it's raining?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "vase",
        status: 0,
        question: "With V, where do many people put flowers?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "winter",
        status: 0,
        question: "With W, which season comes before spring?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "xox",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With X, what would you write if you wanted to end a text message with KISS-CUDDLE-KISS?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "year",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Y, there are 29 days in February in a leap ...?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zero",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, which number is smaller than one?",
    },
];

const preIntermediateQuestionSetThree = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "alligator",
        status: 0,
        question: "With A, which animal is long and looks like a crocodile?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "bicycle",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With B, what has two wheels and can be used to go to school?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "christmas day",
        status: 0,
        question: "With C, what do people call December 25th? (two words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "dentist",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what is the name of a tooth doctor?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "eighteen",
        status: 0,
        question: "With E, what is nine plus nine?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "fat",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With F, what do you call the yellow part on the outside of your steak?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "grandfather",
        status: 0,
        question: "With G, what can you call your father's father?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "hot",
        status: 0,
        question: "With H, how is the weather in the summer?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "in",
        status: 0,
        question: "With I, what is the opposite word to out?",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jeans",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With J, what do people sometimes wear on their legs? They are often blue.",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kick",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, what do football players do with a ball?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "library",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, where can you find lots of books?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "moon",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, what is in the sky at night?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "nose",
        status: 0,
        question: "With N, what body part is in the middle of your face?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "old",
        status: 0,
        question: "With O, a baby is young. What is a grandmother?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "presents",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With P, what do people give friends on their birthdays? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quiz",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Q, what has many questions? Sometimes you can find it in a book or on television.",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "rabbit",
        status: 0,
        question: "With R, which animal has long, floppy ears?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "ship",
        status: 0,
        question: "With S, what is a big boat called?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "talk",
        status: 0,
        question: "With T, what do people do on the telephone?",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "up",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, what is the opposite word to down?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "vegetables",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With V, parents get angry when children don't eat their ... (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "watch",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With W, what can you wear on your wrist to help you tell the time?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "xylophone",
        status: 0,
        question: "With X, this is a musical instrument made of wood.",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yesterday",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Y, the next day is tomorrow. What is the day before today?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zebra",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Z, what is the name of a black and white striped animal?",
    },
];

const intermediateQuestionSetOne = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "afternoon",
        status: 0,
        question: "With A, when do most children go home from school?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "baseball",
        status: 0,
        question: "With B, which sport has a field similar to a diamond shape?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "caterpillar",
        status: 0,
        question: "With C, which bug changes into a butterfly?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "dinosaur",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what was a Tyrannosaurus Rex?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "early",
        status: 0,
        question: "With E, what word is opposite of late?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "fur",
        status: 0,
        question: "With F, humans have hair. What do animals and mammals have?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "glass",
        status: 0,
        question: "With G, what are windows made from?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "handsome",
        status: 0,
        question: "With H, if a woman is beautiful what is a man?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "interview",
        status: 0,
        question: "With I, what do many people have before getting a job?",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jump",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With J, what do football players do before heading the ball?",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "key",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, what do many people use to open or unlock a door?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "lemon",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, which fruit is yellow and oval?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "magician",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With M, who sometimes makes things disappear or pulls a bird or rabbit out of a hat?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "never",
        status: 0,
        question: "With N, what is the opposite word to always?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "open",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With O, shops close at night. What do they do in the morning?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "pe",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With P, what are students studying when they go outside and play sports? (acronym)",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quack",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Q, what noise does a duck make?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "roads",
        status: 0,
        question: "With R, what do cars travel on? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "september",
        status: 0,
        question: "With S, what is the ninth month of the year?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "turkey",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With T, what is the name of the big bird people sometimes eat on special days?",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "uncle",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, the female is an aunt. What is the male?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "vet",
        status: 0,
        question: "With V, what is the name of an animal doctor?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "war",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With W, what do we call it when two countries start fighting?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "axe",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "Contains X, what is the name of the tool that lumberjacks use to chop wood?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yoyo",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Y, what is the name of a toy that goes up and down a string?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zookeeper",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, who cares for the animals at the zoo?",
    },
];

const intermediateQuestionSetTwo = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "argentina",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With A, which South American country is the home of the tango?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "biscuits",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With B, which try snack is loved by both dogs and humans? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "crawl",
        status: 0,
        question: "With C, how do babies move before they start walking?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "dictionary",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what do people use to find the meanings of words?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "eagle",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With E, which big bird has a name that starts and finishes with this letter?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "fan",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With F, what do some people use in the house to cool down on a hot day?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "grass",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With G, what is green and grows on the ground, especially in parks and gardens?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "half",
        status: 0,
        question: "With H, what is the answer to one divided by two?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "islands",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With I, what kind of place is popular for holidays? You probably need a boat to get there. (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jokes",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With J, what do people sometimes tell to make others laugh? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kite",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With K, which kind of toy do children like to fly in the sky?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "lady",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, what is a different word for a woman?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "movie",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, what do you go to the cinema to watch?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "naughty",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With N, what word is used to describe a student who does lots of bad or silly things?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "office",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With O, what kind of place usually has many computers telephones, desjs and workers?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "pilot",
        status: 0,
        question: "With P, who flies an airplane?",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quarter",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Q, what's the name of the US coin that's worth 25 cents?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "robot",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With R, what is run by a computer and sometimes helps humans?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "sunburn",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With S, what do we call it when the sun makes someone's skin very red?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "tick tock",
        status: 0,
        question: "With T, what sound does a clock often make? (2 words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "unicorn",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With U, which mythical horned creature is the national animal of Scotland?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "valentine",
        status: 0,
        question: "With V, which saint is celebrated on the 14th of February?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "wish",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With W, what do people sometimes make before blowing out the candles on their birthday cake?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "taxis",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "Contains X, you will often find many of these vehicles waiting outside the airport? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yogurt",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Y, which dairy product is often eaten as a desert?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zone",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, what is another name for an area? ",
    },
];

const intermediateQuestionSetThree = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "allergy",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With A, if you have a reaction to a food, medicine or cream what do you have?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "bought",
        status: 0,
        question: "With B, what is the past tense of buy?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "cushion",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With C, what do many people sit on to make chairs more comfortable?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "diary",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what do many people write in every day?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "enter",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With E, what is the name of one of the biggest keys on a keyboard?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "forest",
        status: 0,
        question: "With F, what is an area with a lot of treees called?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "ghost",
        status: 0,
        question: "With G, what might you see in a haunted house or graveyard?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "halloween",
        status: 0,
        question: "What special day is October 31st?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "italy",
        status: 0,
        question: "With I, which country looks like a boot on a map?",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jazz",
        status: 0,
        question: "With J, what kind of music often features saxophones?",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kitchen",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, in which room of the house do people normally cook?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "leaves",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, what falls off trees in the fall/autumn? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "mars",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With M, which planet shares its name which a delicious chocolate and caramel snack?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "nuts",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With N, which healthy snack do squirrels like to eat? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "october",
        status: 0,
        question: "With O, what's the name of the 10th month of the year?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "penguin",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With P, what's the name of the black and white bird that can't fly? It's often found in Antartica.",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quickly",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Q, what is the opposite of slowly?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "radio",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With R, what do many people use to listen to music and the news in their car?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "soap",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With S, what do people use when they wash their face or hands?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "tarantula",
        status: 0,
        question: "With T, what is the name of one kind of very big spider?",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "up",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, what is the opposite of down?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "vote",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With V, what do many people do at polling stations during an election?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "weak",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With W, what would you call a person who can't lift heavy things?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "wax",
        status: 0,
        question: "Contains X, which material is often used to make candles?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yard",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Y, what do most houses have outside? (American English)",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zoom",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Z, what do you use if you want to make something bigger on a computer screen?",
    },
];

const intermediateQuestionSetFour = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "address",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With A, what do people write on the envelope before sending a letter?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "bakery",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With B, what is the name for a shop where they make and sell bread?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "customers",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With C, what can we call people who go into shops to buy something? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "dig",
        status: 0,
        question: "With D, what do people do with a space?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "exam",
        status: 0,
        question: "With E, what is a different word for a test?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "france",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With F, what is the name for a large country in Western Europe?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "geography",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With G, in which subject od students learn about the Earth, land, countries and the environment?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "hill",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With H, what do we call somethiing that is like a small mountain, which people walk up and down?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "internet",
        status: 0,
        question: "With I, what do people use on a computer to ",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jigsaw",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With J, what has many small pieces and is a type of picture puzzle?",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kiss",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, what do people sometimes do with their lips?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "late",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, what is the opposite of early?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "mouse",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, which animal can you also find on a computer desk?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "nap",
        status: 0,
        question: "With N, what is a short daytime sleep called?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "owl",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With O, which bird is usually busy at night and sleeps during the day?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "plate",
        status: 0,
        question: "With P, where do people usually serve food?",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quicksand",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Q, what is the name of sand that people can sink in quickly?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "roof",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With R, what is on top of a house and protects it from the elements?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "shampoo",
        status: 0,
        question: "With S, what do people use when they wash their hair?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "trophy",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With T, what do people receive when they win a competition? It's sometimes called a cup.",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "uniform",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, what do many school children wear?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "vanilla",
        status: 0,
        question: "With V, what is the name of a popular flavour of ice cream?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "why",
        status: 0,
        question: "With W, which question word sounds like a letter?",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "maximum",
        status: 0,
        question: "Contains X, what's the opposite of the word minimum?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "year",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Y, what do 365 days make?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zips",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, what do many coats and jackets have? (plural)",
    },
];

const upperIntermediateQuestionSetOne = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "aliens",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With A, what do people call creatures that may live on other planets? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "blueberry",
        status: 0,
        question: "With B, which fruit is blue and very small?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "chef",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With C, what is the person that cooks the food in a restaurant called?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "directions",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With D, take a left, turn right and go straight are all examples of what? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "elbow",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With E, what is the name of the body part in the middle of your arm?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "factory",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With F, what is the name of a place that has many machines and workers and creates many different products?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "great wall of china",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With G, what is the English name for the very long wall in China? (4 words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "hole",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With H, what is the name of the small space that golf players try to hit the ball into?",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "italy",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With I, which European country has green on the left side of its flag, white in the middle and red on the right?",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "january",
        status: 0,
        question: "With J, which month is three months before April?",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kids",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, what is an informal name for children? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "lego",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With L, what is the name of the toy that has many small and colourful plastic bricks?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "million",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, what is one followed by 6 zeros in English? One...",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "newspapers",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With N, what do many people buy and read every day? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "ox",
        status: 0,
        question: "With O, which animal has only two letters in its name?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "parrot",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With P, what is the name for the tropical bird that can also talk?",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "qwerty",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Q, what name is often given to English computer keyboards?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "remote",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With R, what do many people use to change the television channel?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "sundae",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With S, which dessert has a different spelling but sounds the same a day of the week?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "timetable",
        status: 0,
        question: "With T, where can you find the bus or train schedule?",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "unlucky",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, what is the opposite word to lucky?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "veins",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With V, what are the blue lines called that you can see when you look at your skin? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "wigs",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With W, what do some people wear on their head if they don't have much hair? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "expert",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "Contains X, what's the name of a person who is very knowledgeable about a specific topic?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yawn",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Y, what does a tired person do when opening their mouth?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zimbabwe",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, which country borders South Africa?",
    },
];

const upperIntermediateQuestionSetTwo = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "ankle",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With A, what is the name of the joint where the leg and foot meet?",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "balloon",
        status: 0,
        question: "With B, what has a basket and is used for flying?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "camel",
        status: 0,
        question: "With C, which animal has one or two humps on its back?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "duet",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With D, what is it called when two people sing together at the same time?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "eyebrows",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With E, what are the lines of hair on a person's forehead called? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "favourite",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With F, what is it called when something is your most liked? (British English)",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "gold",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With G, what is a yellow metal that is used for jewellery and is usually very expensive?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "hide and seek",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With H, if you do not want your friends to find you, what game are you playing? (3 words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "inch",
        status: 0,
        question: "With I, which measurement is the same as 2.54 centimetres?",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jungle",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With J, what is the name for a place with a lot of trees and vegetation? Tarzan lived there.",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "kitten",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, what is the name for a baby cat?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "lid",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, what is usually on the top of a bottle or a jar?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "mercury",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, which planet is nearest to the Sun?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "needle",
        status: 0,
        question: "With N, what is thin and pointy and used for sewing?",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "onion",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With O, which vegetable sometimes makes people cry when they chop it?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "palace",
        status: 0,
        question: "With P, where would a king or a queen normally live?",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "quill",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Q, what do we call and old fashioned pen that is normally made from a feather?",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "return",
        status: 0,
        question: "With R, which work means come back or go back?",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "sister-in-law",
        status: 0,
        question: "With S, which words describes your spouse's sister?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "telescope",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With T, which object do people use to look at planets and stars?",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "university",
        status: 0,
        question: "With U, where do many people study after high school?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "volcano",
        status: 0,
        question: "With V, what is similar to a mountain but can erupt lava?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "wings",
        status: 0,
        question: "With W, what do birds use to help them fly? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "exhibition",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "Contains X, what do you call a collection of art shown in a gallery or museum?",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "youth",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Y, which word is used to describe somebody who is older than a child but younger than an adult?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zeus",
        status: 0,
        question: "with Z, who was the Greek king of the gods?",
    },
];

const upperIntermediateQuestionSetThree = [
    {
        letter: "a",
        answer: "angel",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With A, what has wings and can fly but is not an animal? It lives in heaven.",
    },
    {
        letter: "b",
        answer: "beard",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With B, what does someone have when they have thick hair over their chin, cheeks and neck?",
    },
    {
        letter: "c",
        answer: "clockwise",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With C, what is the direction called when you move around in the same direction as a clock?",
    },
    {
        letter: "d",
        answer: "divorce",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With D, what is it called when a couple decide to end their marriage?",
    },
    {
        letter: "e",
        answer: "exercise",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With E, swimming, running and hiking are all examples of what?",
    },
    {
        letter: "f",
        answer: "foreigner",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With F, what is the name for a person who comes from another country?",
    },
    {
        letter: "g",
        answer: "gifted",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With G, what do we sometimes call a very, very intelligent person?",
    },
    {
        letter: "h",
        answer: "harbour",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With H, what is the name of a place where people can park their boats other sea vessels? (British English)",
    },
    {
        letter: "i",
        answer: "india",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With I, what is the name of a large Asian country with more than 1 billion inhabitants?",
    },
    {
        letter: "j",
        answer: "jogging",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With J, which activity is faster than walking but slower than running?",
    },
    {
        letter: "k",
        answer: "knife",
        status: 0,
        question: "With K, what do people normally use for cutting?",
    },
    {
        letter: "l",
        answer: "lamb",
        status: 0,
        question: "With L, what is the name for a young sheep?",
    },
    {
        letter: "m",
        answer: "mirror",
        status: 0,
        question: "With M, what do people often look in to see their faces?",
    },
    {
        letter: "n",
        answer: "new year",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With N, what name do many people give to the 1st of January? (2 words)",
    },
    {
        letter: "o",
        answer: "opera",
        status: 0,
        question: "With O, what is the name for a kind of musical drama?",
    },
    {
        letter: "p",
        answer: "pirate",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With P, what kind of person sometimes steals money or commits other crimes at sea?",
    },
    {
        letter: "q",
        answer: "qatar",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With Q, which country begins with the letter Q? Interestingly, it doesn't gave the letter U in its name.",
    },
    {
        letter: "r",
        answer: "rings",
        status: 0,
        question: "With R, what do many people wear on their fingers? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "s",
        answer: "swallow",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With S, after biting and chewing what do we do with the food in our mouths?",
    },
    {
        letter: "t",
        answer: "tusks",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With T, what are an elephants two long teeth called? (plural)",
    },
    {
        letter: "u",
        answer: "umami",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With U, sweet, salty, sour and bitter are often regarded as the 4 tastes. What do somepeople call the 5th taste?",
    },
    {
        letter: "v",
        answer: "volleyball",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "With V, what is the name of a team sport, in which a team can touch the ball three times before hitting it over the net?",
    },
    {
        letter: "w",
        answer: "whisper",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "What is it called when someone talks in a very quiet voice? Sometimes people do this when they tell a secret.",
    },
    {
        letter: "x",
        answer: "anxiety",
        status: 0,
        question:
            "Contains, X, what is the name for the state of feeling nervous or worried that something bad is going to happen? Serious cases can require treatment.",
    },
    {
        letter: "y",
        answer: "yolk",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Y, what is the yellow part in the centre of an egg?",
    },
    {
        letter: "z",
        answer: "zits",
        status: 0,
        question: "With Z, what is another word for spots or acne? (plural)",
    },
];

const allQuestionLists = [
    preIntermediateQuestionSetOne,
    preIntermediateQuestionSetTwo,
    preIntermediateQuestionSetThree,
    intermediateQuestionSetOne,
    intermediateQuestionSetTwo,
    intermediateQuestionSetThree,
    intermediateQuestionSetFour,
    upperIntermediateQuestionSetOne,
    upperIntermediateQuestionSetTwo,
    upperIntermediateQuestionSetThree,
];

export default allQuestionLists;
